

## CONTACTS



+48-577-082-718



xRave110@protonmail.com



Osiedlowa 6, Jabłonka

# **Technologies**

C, Python

Solidity, Javascript

# Toolsets/Frameworks

Pytest

Brownie, Web3, Git

Hardhat/Ethers, React

Truffle, OpenZeppelin

### Other skills

Polish

DeFi

English, Ethereum, ISTQB

NFTs

## Education

#### 2012-2017

## **Cracov University of Technology**

Cracov

Electrical engineering with major in Electric Control Devices in full-time mode of study.

# KAMIL **PALENIK**

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

#### **PROFILE**

I am Software Engineer with 5 years experience in automotive industry. Since 2019 I have got interested in blockchain technology, especially in DeFi. I have started using DeFi protocols and was amazed how it works without any intermediares - just a math and peers.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Dec 2019 - Now

## Blockchain learning/development

Smart contracts development with brownie and unit/integration tests. One year course with Moralis Academy about smart contracts development, web3 interaction and web development. New projects development which consolidated skills and extended them to multiple frameworks and toolsets.

Apr 2022 - Sep 2022

# **Embedded System Software Integrator**

**Nexteer Automotive** 

development. Components Integration tests integration, configuration Autosar stack.

Nov 2019 - Apr 2022

# **Embedded System Software Engineer**

**Nexteer Automotive** 

Developing and testing software components using C, Python and Reactis/Matlab. Incorporating unit and integration testing for CAN messages.

Jun 2019 - 2019 Oct

#### **Embedded Software Engineer**

VECTOR MICROSAR changes in basic software components (DEM, DCM). The same responsibilities as in previous role.

Oct 2017 - May 2019

# **Junior Embedded Software Engineer**

Application component software development. Performing static and dynamic unit tests for components. Modeling software using SysML/UML.